Distortion ripping through the fog and mist.
Downtown sirens where the rebels exist.
Riffs cut corners like they're burning the ground.
Fast lanes bleeding with the punk rock sound.
Speed sign flickers but I don't slow down, don't slow down.
Stereo blaring as I fly through town, fly through town San Fran concrete shakes under tread Not gonna stop for a camera's lead Flash on the avenue, taking monowheels Caught in the web of the automated zeal Big brother's laughing as he flips a reel Speeding in the city pays another meal
Lights flash red as I go Can't stop now, won't slow oh
Pedal to the metal, but the street's all eyes Silent snitches snapping from the lamplight skies Twenty bucks gone in a traffic disguise Every block another Orwell surprise
Ticked it in the inbox, it's a bad routine Punk rock, down shot on the screen Flash on the avenue, taking my wheels Caught in the web of the automated seal Big brother's laughing as he flips the reel Speeding in the city pays another meal Lights flash red as I go Can't stop now, won't slow
Bye.